Previously on desperate housewives...
绝望主妇前情提要...
Do you do weddings?
-你承办婚礼吗
Oh, my goodness. Are you two...
我的老天爷  难道你们俩...
Yes. Yes, we're getting married.
没错  我们要结婚了
Oh, my god! Wow. Congratulations.
恭喜恭喜
Those in love made the next step... Or tried to.
-恋人有了新进展...或者说尝试进展
I need more from you.
我要你给更多
Gaby, I can see them.
-Gaby  我能看见她们了
That's wonderful! Oh!
太棒了
Eyes were opened in more ways than one...
-不只一人得以重见光明...
The key is this doctor guy.
这个医生是关键
Maybe we should just bite the bullet and go to boston.
也许我们该直接杀到波士顿去
You break up my family.
你破坏我的家庭
You burn down my business.
-你毁了我的生意
I didn't burn down your club
我没有烧毁你的俱乐部
And a threat was made.
威胁由此产生
Someday, you'll be walking home from school,
有一天  从学校回家的路上
And you'll just disappear. Poof!
你会突然人间蒸发
There are important events
每个家庭的历史上
In the history of every family...
都有重要事件的发生...
Joyous births...
喜添贵子...
Tragic deaths...
家人猝死...
Sublime weddings.
圣洁婚礼
But the one event every family dreads
然而每一个家庭都害怕的是
Is the moment when they finally meet...
最终见到亲家的...
The in-laws.
那一刻
Mom, this is alex's mom melina cominis.
妈妈  这是Alex的妈妈Melina Cominis
It's a pleasure to meet you.
很高兴见到你
Likewise, and thanks again for letting me stay here.
我也是  再次感谢你让我住在这儿
I just can't afford a motel right now.
我现在已经住不起旅馆了
Oh, alex mentioned that you were laid off from your job.
Alex提起过你刚刚失业了
I'm so sorry.
-深表遗憾
Oh, that's okay.
没事儿
You know what they say-- in a bad economy,
你知道他们怎么说吗  经济危机之下
The mature cocktail waitress is the first to go.
-酒吧女招待最先被炒鱿鱼
Really? They say that?
他们真这样说?
Mom, we're gonna go get your luggage.
我们先去取你的行李
That way, you two can get acquainted.
刚好你们俩可以先聊聊
Thank you again
再次感谢你
For making the long drive down from oakdale.
从Oakdale大老远地赶过来
It's high time our families got together.
正好我们两家聚聚
Absolutely.
当然
Now speaking of family get-togethers,
说起家庭聚会
That reminds me-- I call christmas.
这倒提醒了我  我预定圣诞节
What?
什么?
Now that the boys are getting hitched,
既然孩子们成了一家人
We're gonna have to split the holidays, so...
我们当然也得分开过节假日  所以...
I call christmas.
-我预定圣诞节
Wait, wait, wait.
等等
This is not how we decide family get-togethers.
-我们可不能这样安排家庭聚会
What's the problem?
有何不妥?
I'm letting you have thanksgiving.
我可以把感恩节让给你
I'm a caterer. I oversee events on thanksgiving.
我是个宴会承办人  我感恩节还要工作
It's the one holiday that I don't need.
我不需要那个节日
Great. I call thanksgiving.
很好  那感恩节归我了
Stop that! You can't call all the major holidays.
不行!  你不能霸占所有的重要节日
No one's called easter yet. Going once...
还没人预定复活节  复活节第一次...
I am not bidding on time with my son.
我才不会和人竞标跟儿子相处的时间
Going twice...
-复活节第二次...
Melina, this is childish!
Melina  你太幼稚了!
Ooh! Ooh! My hand's going up.
我的手已经迫不及待了
Fine! I call easter.
好吧!  复活节归我了
That wasn't so hard, was it?
那不是很难  对吧?
Look, I know it's very difficult
听着  我知道两个家庭协商
For two families to negotiate the holidays,
节假日安排并不容易
But I feel strongly
但我强烈认为
That this is not the best way to handle it,
这不是我们解决问题的最好办法
And I'm sure that the boys would agree with me. Hey...
-我相信孩子们也会同意我的看法
I called christmas fair and square,
我可是正大光明地赢了圣诞节
And I wanna spend it with my son.
我想和我儿子一起过
So if you go to the boys and try and screw me over,
如果你在孩子们面前捣鬼  坏了我的好事
I'll remember that for a really long time.
我可是会记恨你很久的
Got it?
明白吧?
Yes, there are important events in the history of every family.
没错  每个家庭的历史上都有重大事件发生...
Meeting the in-laws is one.
亲家见面是其中之一
Look at you two. Have I told you how great you look together?
看看你们俩  我有说过你们俩有多般配吗?
Have i? Aw.
有吗?
The moment you decide to hate them
决定讨厌你亲家的那一刻
Is another.
是其中之二
There's a home for everyone in suburbia,
每一个人都有一栋房子在郊区等着他
And a realtor eager to find you exactly what you want.
还有一位急于投你所好的房产经纪人
Whether it's something warm and cozy...
不管是温暖舒适型...
Or something dignified and elegant...
或者是豪华典雅型...
Or perhaps something affordable with a porch.
还是经济实惠型...
Yes, everyone wants a home with a lovely exterior,
每一个人都需要在郊区拥有一栋可爱的房子
Mostly so the neighbors will never suspect
这样邻居们才不会怀疑
The ugliness going on inside.
房子里的肮脏内幕
There you are!
你在这儿!
I just got the listing for the adams house.
我刚刚拿下了Adams的房子
And I think the best way to celebrate
我想最好的庆祝方式就是
Is for my sexy husband to take me out dancing.
我的性感老公带我去跳舞
Oh, babe. Not tonight.
宝贝儿  今晚不行
What's wrong? Are you sick?
怎么了?  病了吗?
No. No, uh...
不是...
I'm good.
我很好
Really?
是吗?
'cause you look like hell.
因为你看起来糟透了
I'm good, edie. I just, uh...
我很好  Edie  我只是...
I-i just... Feel like staying in tonight, that's all.
我只想今晚上呆在家里  仅此而已
Ah, you're doing it again.
你又来了
There is something upsetting you,
肯定有事让你心烦
And instead of letting me help you,
你非但不肯让我帮你
You're shutting me out.
反而排斥我
I just don't like to talk about my troubles.
我只是不想谈论我的麻烦
And I don't like sitting at home doing nothing
当我想跳舞的时候  我不愿
When I feel like dancing.
呆在家里无所事事
Edie...
I am sorry you're unhappy.
抱歉让你不高兴
There's something you should know about me.
你应该了解我
I don't stay unhappy for long.
我不会一直这么不高兴
Hey, it's jackson,
嘿  我是Jackson
Having fun at the old alma mater.
我在母校玩得很愉快
We need to talk.
我们需要谈谈
Only good news, I promise.
我发誓  只有好消息
Did I mention I miss you? Bye.
我想你  再见
We moved here to get away from that.
我们搬到这儿来就是为了远离那些
I didn't. I moved here for you.
我不是  我搬来是为了你
I've got a deposition to prep for.
我还有案子在身
Well, then I will go clubbing without you,
好吧  那我自己一个人去了
And I will be wearing my "not coming home alone" jeans.
我会穿着我的"不会独自回家"牛仔裤
By "wearing," you mean "squeezing into"?
"穿着"  你是指"塞进去"吧?
Damn you!
去你的!
Miss anything? Need a juicy recap?
错过什么好戏了?  要不要精彩重现?
No. I'm good.
-不  我很好
Boy, you just have to stick your nose
你一定要那么
Into other people's business.
爱管别人的闲事吗
I'm sorry.
对不起
If you're interested, I have dirt on bree.
如果你感兴趣  我知道Bree的丑事儿
Go on.
说吧
You're no better than I am.
你比我好不到哪儿去
Nicely played, mayer.
说得不错  Mayer
Thank you. Can I go clubbing with you tonight?
多谢  我今晚能和你一起混吗?
Overplayed, mayer.
过火了  Mayer
Oh, please! I'm bored.
拜托!  我太无聊了
Mike has m.J., jackson's out of town,
Mike接走了M.J.  Jackson去外地了
And you're gonna need somebody to bitch about bob to.
反正你也需要搭档去气 Bob
You do realize I'm going to a gay club.
你知道我是去同志夜店吧
Yes, that's fine. Gays love me.
没问题  同志喜欢我
Name three.
说出三个人来
You, bob, andrew.
你  Bob  Andrew
That's two.
只有两个
Come on.
拜托
All right, all right!
好吧!  好吧!
Meet at my house at 9:00.
九点去我家碰头
And you might wanna pile on the makeup.
你最好化化妆
Drag queens get their first drink free.
0号(男同性恋中的受方)的第一杯饮料都是免费的
Okay, well, let's try something easier.
好吧  我们从更简单的问题开始
After you left mr. Schilling's nightclub,
你离开Schilling先生的俱乐部
Where did you go first?
之后去了哪儿
I don't recall.
我不记得了
Did you maybe drive somewhere?
你有可能开车去了某个地方吗
Okay, porter, when the d.A., who also has this police report,
Poter  地方检察官也有警方报告
Asks you these questions,
当他问你这些问题的时候
And you suddenly "don't recall" anything you said,
你突然"不记得"你所说过的一切
That's bad.
那对你不利
Bob, you've been going at this for over an hour.
Bob  你已经问了一个小时了
Why don't we take a break?
-不如稍作休息吧
Fine. Porter, go and chill.
好  Porter  去那边乘凉吧
I need to talk to your parents anyway.
我也得跟你父母谈谈
Okay, what's going on here?
这到底是怎么回事?
Nothin'. You know, porter's just nervous.
没什么  Porter只是很紧张罢了
He was also nervous when I first interviewed him in jail,
我跟他在拘留所里第一次谈的时候他也很紧张
But he was still able to keep his story straight.
但至少能讲清事情的来龙去脉
Preston! Where's my cd player?!
Preston!  我的CD播放机在哪儿?
What?
什么?
Parker saw you take it.
Parker说他看见你拿了
Mom, please tell preston to stop taking my stuff.
妈妈  告诉Preston别再拿我的东西了
Honey, that's porter.
亲爱的  那是Porter
No, it isn't.
不  他不是
Oh. Right.
哦  对
Sorry.
对不起
You guys have something you wanna tell me?
你们有没有什么想要和我分享的啊?
Gaby, you should've come.
Gaby  你应该和我们一起的
You missed a beautiful walk in the park.
你错过了一次在公园散步的美好时光
Mommy, look at what we found! A ladybug!
妈妈看我们找到了什么  一只瓢虫
Wow! Neat!
哇  真可爱
Why don't you guys go wash your hands for lunch?
你们快去洗手吃饭啦
Oh, look at her teeny black polka dots.
看它身上的小圆点点多可爱
There's so many beautiful things I used to take for granted
在我双目失明以前
Before I lost my sight.
有太多的美好事物被我忽略了
Yeah, pretty.
是啊  真漂亮
What? You're gonna be late for work.
怎么了?  你上班要迟到了
Yeah, about that...
关于那个...
I should've told you before...
我应该早点告诉你的...
What?
什么?
I don't want to give massages anymore,
我不想再给人按摩了
So I quit the country club.
所以呢我辞职了
You quit?! Why?
你辞职了?  为什么?
Okay, I know this is gonna sound bad...
我知道这听起来有点别扭...
When I was blind, I never realized that...
我失明的时候  从来没觉得...
Naked people are gross, especially the middle-aged slobs
裸体的人很恶心  特别是那些乡村俱乐部里
That belong to this country club.
中年发福的胖子
Carlos, you don't just quit a job
Carlos  你不能因为人们背上
Because of a few moles and a little back fat.
-多长了些肉就辞掉工作
But I can find other work.
但是我可以找别的工作
Now that I have my vision back, the world is my oyster.
现在我的视力恢复了  世界又在我掌控之中了
In the meantime,
再说
I just wanna spend a few days with my daughters
我也想跟女儿们多呆一下
And smelling the roses, soaking in nature.
闻闻玫瑰花香  沉浸在大自然中
Like that beautiful spider right there.
就像这只美丽的蜘蛛一样
God's perfect design.
真是上帝完美的创作啊
Isn't it amazing?
难道你不惊叹么?
Yeah, it sure is.
是的  当然
I'll get you the want ads.
我给你拿招聘广告
What's all this?
-这是些什么?
Oh, andrew thought it would be nice
Andrew觉得明天晚上准备
To have a formal dinner tomorrow night.
一次正式的晚宴能让我们尽到地主之谊
Well, if it's a formal dinner,
如果是次正式的晚宴
Why aren't we using your grandmother's tablecloth?
为什么不用你外婆的桌布?
For melina? She'd probably blow her nose on it.
招待Melina?  她很有可能会朝上面打喷嚏的
No, I will not let that woman defile nana's lace.
我可不想让那个女人弄脏外婆的蕾丝桌布
I know melina isn't what we hoped for,
我知道Melina不如我们所望
But let's face it-- in-laws rarely are.
但是面对现实吧  亲家有几个让人满意呢
Need I remind you of my mother?
有必要提提我妈妈吗?
Well, at least gloria had the good taste
至少Gloria很识相的
To have a paralyzing stroke
得了中风瘫在那儿了
So we don't have to deal with her.
所以我们不用对付她了
True. That was a merry christmas.
是啊  真是谢天谢地
But melina appears to be in tragically good health,
但很不幸  貌似Melina健康状况很好
Which means we've got
也就是说
Quite a few beer-drenched holidays ahead of us.
有一连串的好戏等着我们呢
You have got to figure out some way to be nice to her.
你要想点办法对她好一点
I don't know if I have it in me. She's such a troglodyte.
我可不确定我能做到  她真像个原始人
Please.
拜托
No one's better
没有人
At plastering on a fake smile and pretending to like someone
比Bree Hodge更擅长用假笑
Than bree hodge.
来佯装喜欢对方了
Mmm. You're sweet.
你真贴心
Oh, all right. Get the lace tablecloth.
好吧  用外婆的蕾丝桌布
I will pretend to like this woman.
我要假装喜欢这个女人
Just like I pretended to like nana.
就像我假装喜欢外婆一样
Bob, we're so sorry. We meant to tell you. We really did.
Bob  真的很抱歉  我们原本打算告诉你的  真的
So where the hell is porter?
-那Poter到底去哪儿了?
We don't know.
我们也不知道
That's why we've been trying to get you
这就是为什么我们想让你
To postpone the hearing date until we could find him.
把听证日延期  直到我们找到他
Oh, we have a much bigger problem than the hearing date
我们有比听证日更严重的问题了
What do you mean?
-此话怎讲?
Well, now that I'm aware of this,
我现在知道了这件事
I have a legal obligation to report it.
-我有法律义务报告它
What?! No, no, no, you can't--
什么?  不  你不能...
No! We can't-- hey!
-不  我们不能这样
Now my hands are tied.
现在我被套住了
But if the judge finds out that porter's gone,
但是如果法官知道Porter不见了
We have to forfeit the bail.
我们的保释金会被没收
And since my genius wife used our restaurant to post bond
而且我的天才老婆把我们的餐馆做了抵押
Our only source of income will vanish.
这样一来我们的唯一收入来源就没了
I feel for you guys. I really do.
我很理解你们  真的
But I'm not getting disbarred over this.
但我不能放任你们这样做
Bob... Please. We're desperate.
Bob...拜托了  我们很绝望
I'm not meeting with the d.A. For another two days.
我这两天不会见地方检察官
If you find porter by then, I won't say anything.
如果你们在此之前找到他  我就当什么都不知道
Thank you so much. We are so sorry that we--
太感谢了  我们真的很抱歉...
Just find him.
赶紧去找他吧
Yeah, yeah. I'm comin'.
好了  好了  我来了
Gabrielle solis?
Bradley scott. Remember?
Bradley scott  记得吗?
Carlos and I did some business back in his finance days.
我和Carlos以前做过生意的
Oh, right! How are you?
对啊  你好吗
Good. Maria and I finally got married.
很好  Maria和我结婚了
I started my own investment fund.
我自己创办了投资基金会
How about yourself?
-你自己怎么样
Good, good.
很好  很好
I don't know if you heard-- carlos got
我不知道你听说没有...
His sight back.
-Carlos复明了
Oh, my--my god. I had no idea
天呐  我还不知道呢
I know. Life is good.
我知道  生活很美好
Now all we have to do is find him a job.
现在唯一要做的就是给他找个工作
Well, your timing just might be perfect here.
-你们的时机真是太好了
Why? You need someone?
为什么  你缺人吗
As a matter of fact, I do. Think he'd be interested?
事实上  是这样  他有兴趣吗
I don't know. I-i can't speak for carlos.
我不知道  我不能替Carlos做主
It's an upper-level position with lots of perks
这是个高层职位  有很多补贴的
And the salary's in the high six figures.
而且薪水高达6位数
I'm now speaking for carlos. He'll take it.
-现在我就为Carlos做主了  他答应了
Great.
太好了
I'd kill to have carlos on my team. That man was a shark.
我等不及Carlos加入我的团队了  他是员猛将
Have him call me.
-叫他打给我
Yeah.
好的
So long, sucka.
拜拜咯  衰人
Hello. Is dr. Heller in?
你好  Heller医生在里面吗
I'm sorry. He's not. Can I help you?
对不起  他不在  我能帮你什么吗
Oh. Not really.
恐怕不行
See, we need to talk to him about dave williams.
我们得跟他谈谈Dave Williams
Dave williams?
Dave Williams?
Yeah. Dave is a patient of his.
是的  Dave是他的一个病人
I'm sure you know him--
我确定你认识他...
Blond hair, blue eyes, creepier than all get-out.
金色头发  蓝眼睛  比所有人都诡异
I'm not in a position to confirm that. Hmm.
我不能随便透露病人资料
Ah? And I don't think the doctor
我觉得医生也不会
Would discuss his patients with you either.
-和你谈论他的病人
Oh, he'll talk to us.
他会和我们谈的
Dave's been up to some pretty sick stuff...
-Dave想要做一些非常肮脏的事情...
Yeah.
是的
And i-i'm bettin' dollars to doughnuts dr. Heller
我打赌Heller医生
Would wanna know all about it.
会想要知道
So when does he get here?
-那他什么时候到?
I couldn't say.
我不能说
Huh. We'll wait.
那我们等他
Is that a beer?
那是啤酒吗
We're not in a position to confirm that.
我们不能告诉你
Your new shoes are pretty.
你的新鞋真漂亮
Aren't they? Daddy bought them for mommy--
可不是吗  爸爸给妈妈买的...
He doesn't know it yet--
但他还不知道...
Because he has a wonderful new job.
因为他将有一份很棒的新工作
He doesn't that yet either.
这他也还不知道
Good news!
好消息!
Me, too. Me first.
我也有好消息  我先说
Remember bradley scott?
你还记得Bradley Scott吗
I ran into him today, and he's giving you a job.
我今天碰见他了  他要给你一个工作
That's... Nice.
那...不错
But that's what I wanted to tell you.
但那也是我要告诉你的
I just got a job.
-我刚找到了份工作
Fantastic!
太好了!
Well, you didn't sign a contract or anything, did you?
你还没签合同或任何东西吧?
'cause maybe we can get them into a bidding war.
因为我们可以让这两份工作来为你抬价
Unlikely. It's at the community center.
不太可能  这工作在社区中心
I'm gonna work with the blind.
我要和盲人一起工作
Oh. Great.
好啊
And what's the signing bonus for that--a cup of pencils?
这份工作可以得到什么分红...一罐铅笔吗?
I thought you were gonna get a better job.
我以为你要找一份更好的工作呢
What happened to the world being your oyster?
让你觉得前途无限美好的世界怎么了
It's meaningful work.
-这很有意义
Who cares? Bradley's offering perks.
我不在乎  Bradley要给你分红的
What kind of perks is this blind thing offering?
这份盲人工作能给你什么好处?
Hmm, let me think...
让我想想...
Making the world a better place, personal fulfillment.
让世界更美好  个人更充实
Carlos, I've spent the last five years working with the blind.
Carlos  我过去5年都在和盲人一起工作
Trust me, it's not that fulfilling.
相信我   没那么充实有意义
Look, when I lost my sight, those people were there for me.
听着  当我失明的时候  那些人帮助了我
Ah, I just wanna give something back.
我只是想要回报给他们
Not to mention...
更不用说...
Bradley scott?
Bradley Scott
Kind of an ass.
基本上是个混蛋
No way I'm working for that guy.
我不可能为他工作
Hi, bradley, it's gaby solis.
你好  Bradley  我是Gaby Solis
I just talked to him, and he's intrigued.
我刚跟他谈了  他很有兴趣
How would you like to come over for dinner
你愿意过来吃个晚饭
And seal the deal?
然后把这事定了?
This is so fun! I haven't been out in ages.
真好玩  我好久都没出来玩过了
Tonight, I am gonna...
今晚  我要...
You really haven't been out in a while.
你还真是很久没出来了
Oh! Go ahead. What do you want to drink?
接吧  你想喝什么
Oh, I'll have what you're having.
-你喝什么我就喝什么
Cirrhosis of the liver, coming right up.
肝硬化  马上来
Hey, jackson.
Jackson
What?
什么?
Really?
真的?
Ah! Here you are.
你在这里啊
Yeah, just taking in the scenery.
是啊  你不看到了吗
You know, we actually have
实际上  我们在后院
Some very comfortable patio furniture in the backyard...
有非常舒服的露台可以小酌...
Along with a place to put your recyclables.
还有一个让你扔垃圾的垃圾桶
No, I'm good here.
不  我在这很好
Hey! Hi! What have you two been up to?
你们两个去干嘛了?
Edie was showing us some houses.
Edie带我们两个看房子去了
I didn't know know you two were house hunting
我不知道你们两个在找房子
Yes. We've got to get out of that
是的  我们得从那公寓里搬走
Apartment. Did edie show you the adams house
Edie有给你们看Adams的房子吗
She did, and it's fantastic.
-看了  那很不错
And if we could figure out a way to move it
如果我们有办法让它移到
Next to a toxic waste dump, maybe we could afford it.
有毒垃圾倾倒站附近的话  我们可能就能买得起了
Holy moly, would you look at these prices!
天哪  你看看这价格
You know, for this kind of money,
知道吗  用这些钱
You could come up to my town
你们到我那里
And get a 5-bedroom house on the lake.
都可以买一栋湖边有5间卧室的大房子了
I'm sure they could.
我想也是
It's too bad your practice is all the way down here.
但是很遗憾你的诊所就开在这里
It is now,
那是现在
But it's not like there aren't sick people in oakdale.
Oakdale又不是没有病人
Who, undoubtedly, already have doctors,
当然有  但是那里的病人也已经有医生了吧
Just like your patients in fairview have you.
就像是美景镇的病人有你这个医生了一样
Fine. Let them stay in that teeny apartment.
好吧  就让他们待在那个小公寓吧
Who cares if the other doctors make fun of you?
谁在乎是否会有其他医生嘲笑你?
You know, I think we should talk about this.
我想我们得谈谈这事
You'd really like oakdale--
你会喜欢Oakdale的...
No traffic, fresh air.
没有堵车  空气清新
Hey, I'm open.
我很开明的
Maybe we can go up there this weekend and look around.
也许这周末我们可以去那里看看
What are you doing?
你在做什么
Just helping the boys live the american dream.
帮助孩子们实现美国梦般的生活
I'll tell you what.
我告诉你吧
If the guys move up near me,
如果孩子们搬到离我近的地方住
You can have 'em for christmas.
你就能和他们一起过圣诞
I just wish there was some way I could get back at bob.
我只希望有办法能报复一下Bob
I'm so sick of his smug attitude.
我真讨厌他那自以为是的态度
"i'm the provider. I bring home the bacon."
"我在养家  我赚钱回家"
Well, you know what? I contribute, too.
你知道吗  我也有贡献啊
I handle the bills. I clean the house.
我处理账单  我打扫房子
I thought you had a housekeeper.
我以为你们有管家呢
Jeez, you're an ugly drunk.
天啊  你的醉态真丑
Come on. It's a joke.
我开玩笑的
What's with the face?
你什么表情啊?
I just...
我只是...
Jackson called earlier, and, um...
Jackson刚才打电话...
You know, he went to riverton to visit his old art professor,
他去了Riverton看他的老教授
And she offered him a job.
她给他提供了一份工作
That's cool.
那很好啊
And he wants me to move there with him.
他想要我搬去和他一起
You gonna go?
你会去吗
I wanna be with him, so...
我想和他在一起  所以...
I think I have to.
我想我不得不
You're that serious about this guy?
你对这家伙挺认真的嘛?
Yeah. Sure.
是的  当然
Why not?
为什么不呢
You sure you're not just waiting for closing time?
你确定你不是在酒吧要关门的时候胡乱找一个人?
What does that mean?
什么意思?
You know, 2:00 a.M., bar's closing.
凌晨2点  酒吧要关门了
You haven't found the perfect guy,
你都还没找到完美的那个人
So you settle for... Something like that.
所以你就随便找了个...像那样的
Oh, crap. Look away. Look away. Look away.
糟糕  别看那边  别看那边
Lee, that is not what I'm doing. Is jackson perfect? No.
Lee  我没有像你说的那样  Jackson完美吗?  不
But I don't think there is such a thing,
但我不相信世上有谁是完美的
And I have a history of sabotaging relationships.
而且我有找错对象的"劣迹"
No, I'm doing this.
我确定  我要这么做
I'm moving.
我要搬过去
Well, congratulations to you.
那就祝贺你了
Uh-oh. Scary guy's coming over.
吓人的家伙走过来了
I have to throw him off the scent.
我得让他死心
Do you mind if I grab one of your boobs?
-你介意我碰你的胸部吗
Oh! Knock yourself out.
没关系  随便
Oh! Jazz!
爵士乐!
Oh, my god!
天哪
Why didn't you wake me?! Bob is going to kill me.
你为什么不叫醒我?  Bob会杀了我的
But that was, uh, fun last night.
不过昨晚上真的很有趣
Different, but fun.
不同的感觉  但很有趣
See ya. Aah!
再见
Tom, I talked to every kid in his english class,
Tom  我已经问过他英语班的所有同学
The entire debate team.
和整个辩论队
Porter hasn't contacted any of them.
Porter没有和他们任何人联系过
Well, hurry home. We gotta decide what our next move is.
快点回家  我们得决定下一步怎么做
All right. I love you. Bye.
好的  我爱你  再见
Preston, why didn't you pick up when I called you?
Preston  我给你打电话怎么不接
What?
-什么?
I called you, like, five times.
我给你电话了  打了五次了
No, you didn't.
-没  你没有
Yeah.
我打了
See? You're not even on my call log. Oh.
看  你都没在我通话记录里
Hey, dude. Is mom still there?
喂  老兄  妈还在吗
Porter, it's mom. Where are you?!
Porter  是妈妈  你在哪?!
Porter!
Porter
You know where he is!
-你知道他在哪
I don't. He won't tell me.
我不知道  他不告诉我
But you have been talking to him. What the hell, preston?!
但你一直和他通话  怎么回事  Preston
I want my phone back.
-把电话还我
Fine. You know what you're going to do with it?
好  你知道你该怎么做吗
You are going to call your brother
你要给你兄弟打电话
And tell him to come home.
-告诉他回家
He's not coming home.
他不会回家的
Mr. Schilling threatened to kill him.
-Schilling恐吓说要杀了他
What? What?! That's why he ran away?
所以他就逃跑了?
I thought he was afraid of going to jail.
我原以为他怕蹲监狱
Well, I'm sure warren schilling was just trying to scare him.
我确定Warren Schilling只是想吓唬吓唬他
It worked! Porter's terrified!
他的恐吓的确管用了  Porter吓到了
Okay, we'll get a--we'll get a restraining order.
那好  我们  我们去弄个法庭禁令
I don't think that's gonna stop this guy.
-那不会管用
I can handle warren schilling.
我能处理Warren Schilling这件事
But if porter doesn't show up for court,
但是如果Porter不出庭
We're gonna lose our restaurant!
-我们的餐厅就没了
A guy threatens to kill your son,
有人恐吓说要杀你儿子
And that's what you're worried about?
而你所担心的就是这个?
No, I'm not gonna let my brother risk his life
不  我才不会让我兄弟冒生命危险
So you and dad can sell pizza.
好让你和老爸继续卖披萨
How do you sleep with someone and not remember?
你怎么能和人家上了床还不记得了
I don't know. I was drunk.
我也不知道  我喝多了
Okay, let's skip to the important part--who was it?
那好  咱们跳到重要部分  是谁?
Just a friend.
只是个朋友
Oh, gaby,
Gaby
Do you think I did this subconsciously
你觉得我这样做是在潜意识地
Just to sabotage my relationship with jackson?
破坏我和Jackson的关系吗?
It was tom scavo, wasn't it?
是不是Tom Scave
Will you stop guessing?
能不能别瞎猜了
Oh, god! Why won't I just let myself be happy?
为什么我就不能让自己高兴点呢
Was it lou?
是Lou吗
My mechanic? Are you crazy?
我的修理工?  你疯啦
Come on. You were with a plumber and a housepainter.
得了吧  你跟过水管工还有漆工
I mean, let's face it-- you like your service providers.
面对事实吧  你喜欢为你服务的人
Susan, you home?
Susan  你在家吗
Bob! Um...
Bob
Uh, what are you doing here?
你有事吗
Well... It's about lee.
是跟Lee有关
He told me he took you out last night.
他跟我说他昨晚带你出去了
Yes. Uh, we had a very nice, uneventful evening. Why?
是啊  我们过了一个很好很平静的夜晚  怎么了
What did he say?
他说什么了吗
'cause he was pretty drunk,
因为他醉得挺厉害
So he was... Probably making stuff up.
所以他  可能会乱讲话
Well, he didn't come home.
他昨晚没回家
He claims he spent the night here.
他说在这过的夜
Oh, my god.
天哪
Oh, hi, gaby. I didn't know you were
嗨  Gaby  我不知道你在
Here. Never mind her. She was just leaving
别管她  她要走了
No. I think I should stay and clean this up.
不  我觉得我得把这清理一下
It's a... Huge mess.
这真是...太乱了
Uh, bob...
Bob...
Uh, lee did stay here last night.
Lee昨晚确实在这
He slept on the couch... In the guest room.
他睡在沙发上...客房的沙发
So you have nothing to worry about. Oh,
所以你不用太担心
Thank god. I just had this awful feelin
谢天谢地  我只是感觉不太好
That he spent the night with another man.
总觉得他和别的男人过夜了
Lee wouldn't do that. He loves you.
Lee不会那样做的  他很爱你的
I know he does,
我知道
But he's got a few drinks in him,
但一旦他沾了酒
He'll bang anything with a pulse and facial hair.
他会和任何活着的有体毛的东西性交
You still haven't heard from him?
你还没有他的消息?
For the 17th time...
第十七次回答...
No.
没有
Where does she get off having all that attitude?
这妞儿哪来的  态度怎么这样
She's young and pretty, and we're not.
人家年轻貌美  我们人老珠黄
She's not that pretty.
她也没那么美啊
I can hear every word you're saying.
我能听见你们说的一字一句
From all the way over there? Boy, she is young.
这么远都能听见?  老天  她确实是年轻
Look, I'm very tired, so I'm going to break the rules.
听着  我现在很累了  所以我不得不违规了
Dr. Heller went on some sort of trip.
Heller医生好像出门了
He should've been back a week ago,
他本该一周前回来
And I don't know where he is.
我也不知道他在哪
Why didn't you tell us that in the first place
你怎么不事先跟我们讲
Because it's none of your business!
因为那不干你们鸟事
Hello? Dr. Heller's office.
你好  Heller医生办公室
Uh, hey. It's david dash. Is he in?
你好  我是David Dash  他在吗
Did you hear that? He should've been back by now.
你听见了吗  他本该回来了
Why isn't he back?
为什么他没回来
I'm sorry, mr. Dash. Dr. Heller's out of town.
不好意思  Dash先生  Heller医生出城了
What are you saying? You think dave has something to do
你什么意思  你是说Dave和Heller医生晚回来
With heller being late from vacation?
有关系吗?
Don't ask me why, but I got a feeling there's a connection.
别问我原因  但我就感觉有某种联系
Well, can I still get a prescription refilled?
那我能拿到我的配药处方吗
Sure.
当然
Dr. Lybrand's on call.
Lybrand医生出诊
Could you see him tomorrow around 2:00?
你能明天下午两点左右过来吗
Actually, I've moved.
其实  我搬家了
You know what?
你知道吗
What?
什么
I'm done.
我不干了
Meaning what?
什么意思
I'm sure we can work it out. What's your new address?
那不是问题  你的新地址是?
What, you're just gonna abandon me?
你要就这么甩下我?
I went on this wild goose chase as far as I could
这事我瞎忙活时间够长了
Oh, don't--please don't go, roberta.
别  Roberta  别走
I need your help.
我需要你
Then get somebody else. I'm tapped out.
找别人吧  我出局
Roberta, wait!
Roberta  等等
"wisteria lane." what a lovely name.
紫藤街  多好听的名字
Bree, you sure there isn't anything I can do to help?
Bree  你确定没什么我可以帮忙的
I'm just standing here with my thumb up my butt.
我只是在这拇指掐腰站着
Uh, no help needed.
没什么可帮忙
Certainly nothing that would require your thumb.
当然没什么需要你的拇指帮忙的
Hey. Uh, sorry we're late. We got hung up at the realtors.
不好意思迟到了  我们刚去了房产经纪人那
Actually, you're right on time. We're just about to eat.
事实上  你们来的正好  正要开饭呢
Shall we? Yeah.
来吧
Hmm. Excuse...
不好意思...
Excuse me, melina. That's my chair.
不好意思  Melina  这是我的位置
I just wanted to sit next to the boys.
我只是想挨着孩子们坐
Well, did it occur to you
你可曾想到
I might want to sit next to the boys?
我也许也想和孩子们坐在一起
Did it occur to you that I already called it?
那你可曾知道我已经早占了这位子?
She did. She called it.
她确实说过
Why don't you sit here, bree?
你坐这来吧  Bree
Guess who just called the burnt lamb chop?
猜猜谁点了烧焦的羊排
I just wanted to see the look on your faces
我只是想看看你们的表情
When you heard my good news.
当我宣布好消息的时候
Really? What is it?
真的吗  是什么
Well, I told dr. Hardy you're moving to oakdale.
我跟Hardy医生说你要搬回Oakdale
Uh, thinking about it.
在考虑中
They're thinking about moving to oakdale.
他们正在考虑搬去Oakdale
Not after they hear this.
听完这个他们就不用考虑了
Anyway, he's retiring next month,
他下个月就退休了
And he thinks you'd be perfect to take over his practice.
他觉得你来接替他是最适合不过得了
Are you serious? Wow, this could be a good opportunity for us.
你当真?  这对我们来说真是个好机会
Yes. A good opportunity
是  是个好机会
For andrew to commute five hours to his job.
让Andrew开五个小时的车来上班
I don't know, alex. This is all happening pretty fast.
我不知道  Alex  这事发展太快了
But it's the only way we're gonna be able to afford a house,
但这是我们能供起房子唯一的途径
And if we're gonna have kids...
-如果我们将来有孩子的话...
You're gonna have kids?
你们要养孩子?
Oh, this is perfect! I can look after them for you!
太完美了!  我可以为你们照看孩子!
Oh! Let's toast to seal the deal.
就这么定了  让我们干杯庆祝下
Here's to oakdale.
为Oakdale干杯
I bought you the adams house!
我给你们买了Adams的房子!
What?
什么?
What?!
-什么?!
What?
什么
It was going to be a surprise, you know, for your wedding.
我本想给你们的婚礼一个惊喜
Unfortunately, this whole silly oakdale thing
但是  这个搬到Oakdale的愚蠢计划
Has forced me to show my hand.
使我不得不提早透露
Mom, that's too generous.
妈  你太慷慨了
Yes, that's, uh...
是的  实在是...
That's way too generous. You shouldn't do that.
非常慷慨  你用不着这样
Oh, it's nothing you wouldn't do.
作为母亲  任何事都是乐意之至的
Bree, I don't know what to say, except...
Bree  我不知该说什么  唯有...
Thank you so much.
非常感谢
I really love you for this.
我爱死你了
Oh, and I love you, too.
我也爱你
Orson, dear, would you pour melina another glass of wine?
Orson  亲爱的  可以再为Melina倒一杯红酒吗
Calling edie, are you?
给Edie打电话是吧?
You know it.
当然
Hi, honey. You remember bradley and his wife maria.
亲爱的  还记得Bradley和他太太Maria吗?
They dropped by for dinner.
他们顺路来用晚餐
How fun.
有意思
Can I ask you something about the trash cans?
我能问你几个跟垃圾桶有关的问题吗
Excuse me.
稍等片刻
What is that miserable s.O.B. Doing here?
那个面目可憎的家伙来这做什么?
I already took the job at the community center.
我已经接了社区中心的工作
I know. Just listen to what bradley has to say,
我知道  不过听听Bradly会说什么
And if at the end of the evening you're still not interested,
如果晚餐结束你还是不感兴趣
I support you completely. Deal?
我就无条件支持你  怎样?
If it'll get you off my back... Deal.
如果能让你不再烦我...成交
After I got concessions from the union,
得到联邦政府许可后
I laid off a third of the workforce,
我削减了三分之一的员工
Outsourced another third.
将另外三分之一员工外包
A year later, I sold the company for twice what I paid for it.
一年之后  我以购买价的两倍卖出公司
Wow. Impressive. Huh, carlos?
-太帅了  是吧  Carlos?
Very.
怎么不是呢
It'll be a great story to tell all the other c.E.O.S in hell.
对任何境遇窘迫的CEO们都是绝佳的故事
Carlos, be nice.
Carlos  和善点
No, it's fine. Just taking care of my kids.
没关系  只是为了能照顾好我的孩子们
Yeah. I've got a picture of them in my purse.
我皮包里有他们的照片
Wanna see how many you can name?
想试试你能叫出几个人的名字吗?
More wine, maria?
给你添点酒  Maria?
So, bradley, if carlos were to come work for you,
那么  Bradley  如果Carlos来你公司的话
What would a typical week look like?
每周都要做些什么?
Oh, lots of high-end deal making,
很多交易的高端决策
Uh, international travel.
国际商务旅行
Oh, yeah. We travel all over the world together.
没错  我们一起环球旅行
It is so fun sitting alone in a five-star hotel
实在是很有意思  当你一个人端坐在五星级酒店
While your husband is out crushing the third world
而你的丈夫则在外  用他的铁腕手段
Under the heel of his jackboot.
狠狠地征服第三世界
You hear that, carlos? Five-star hotels.
你听见了吗  Carlos?  五星级酒店耶
Listen, bradley,
听着  Bradley
Really appreciate the offer,
很感谢你提供工作机会
But I told you-- I already have a job.
但是我告诉你  我已经有工作了
Why can't you do your work with the deaf on the weekends?
你就不能周末的时候和那帮聋子一起工作吗
First of all, because they're blind.
首先  他们是盲人
You tell him.
你告诉他
Um, honey, bradley's right. You could take this job
亲爱的  Bradley说的没错  你可以接下这份工作
And do your charity work in your free time.
然后利用空余时间做慈善工作呀
No, don't listen to her. You are a good man,
别听她的话  你是个好男人
And you are going to help people.
你要去帮助人们
And even if you'll ever end up making a penny,
就算收入少得可怜
You'll be worth more than this soulless bastard.
身价也比这个没良心的杂种高多了
I work very hard to provide for you and the kids,
我辛辛苦苦工作  为的是让你和孩子们衣食无忧
And I would like a little respect.
我希望得到一点尊重
Well, you know what I would like? A big divorce.
那么  你知道我希望得到什么?  离婚
So...
那么...
Is eye care included in the health plan?
医保中包括眼科治疗吗
'cause that's obviously a big issue for carlos.
很显然  Carlos需要这个
Daddy misses you so much.
爸爸好想你们
I'm so sorry.
我对不起你们
Okay?
好吗
Bye-bye! I miss you two so much.
再见!  我好想你们
Very soon, honey.
很快了  亲爱的
It's just a little teeny bit longer.
只比预计的再多那么点时间
Oh, my little girl.
我的乖女儿
You look so beautiful.
你好漂亮
I've missed you so much.
我一直都好想你们
We're gonna be together soon. I promise you.
很快我们就能团聚了  我保证
Just a teeny little bit. It'll be fine.
-再多一点点时间  一切都会好了
Dave?
I'm sorry. You scared me.
对不起  你吓到我了
Who were you talking to?
你在和谁说话?
No one.
没谁
I heard you.
我听到了
Edie, please, j--
Edie  请谅解  我...
I'm not feeling well.
我不大舒服
Who the hell were you talking to?
你到底在和谁说话?
Leave me alone.
别管我
Why did you turn down here?
怎么把车开这来了?
I thought we were going to the store.
我们不是去商店吗?
Mom, what is this place?
妈  这是哪?
Before I became a mother,
在我成为母亲前
I didn't know it was possible
我不知道我会如此
To love another human being so completely,
无私地爱着另外一个人
And with that love comes this need to protect you.
正是因为这种爱  我才想保护你们
It wasn't a decision I made.
这不是我作出的决定
It's... Primal.
这是...本能
It's just something in my d.N.A.
一种潜伏在我基因中的物质
Whatever it is,
且不管它是什么
It makes me not care about myself,
这使得我不再看重自己
And it reminds me
并且提醒我
That my reason for being on this planet
我之所以存在在这地球
Is to look after you kids.
是为了要照顾我的孩子
Why are you telling me this?
为什么要告诉我这些?
Yesterday, you said
昨天你说
Warren schilling will kill porter
Warren Schilling一旦找到机会
If he gets the chance.
便会杀了Porter
I will never let that happen.
我不会让他得手的
Mom, where are we?
妈  这是哪?
You see that bar?
看见那酒吧没?
Warren schilling goes there every night.
Warren Schilling每晚都去那
All right, come on!
好吧  快点
Tonight, when he leaves...
今晚  他离开的时候...
I'm gonna do what I have to, to make sure my family is safe.
我要采取必要措施  来保护我的家人
So...
所以...
I need you to get out now.
你现在离开车子
You can't be in the car when this happens.
我行动的时候你不可以在车内
Are you serious?
你真的要这么做?
You're gonna run him over?
撞死他?
Like I said, it's in my d.N.A.
我说过了  这是本能
That could be him.
那可能是他
Get out.
出去
Get out! Get out!
出去  出去!
Okay! Stop it! I get it! I'll call porter and tell him
住手  我知道了  我会打电话给Porter
He doesn't have to worry about mr. Schilling.
告诉他不用害怕Schilling
And you will convince him to come back home.
而且要说服他回家
Shut the door.
关上门
So...
那么
Remember how you said I just had to hear bradley out,
还记得你说过的吗  说我只要好好听Bradley讲完
And then whatever I decided, you'd support me?
然后无论我做什么决定  你都会支持我?
Well, you may be surprised,
你也许会吃惊
But I am ready to render my decision.
我准备作出决定了
Let me lay it out for you--
听我跟你说说...
Either I do something fulfilling
要么我做自己心仪的工作
Where I help other people and feel good about myself,
可以帮助别人  自我感觉良好
Or I take a job I hate where I make a lot of money,
或者我接受一份我讨厌的工作  赚很多钱
But it eats my life and crushes my soul.
任其消磨我的生命  泯灭我的灵魂
Hang on. Before you do that, let me lay it out for you.
停  在你做出选择之前先听我说说
Either you let your family continue to sacrifice
要么令你的家人继续为你牺牲
So you can feel good about yourself,
让你保持自我感觉良好
Or you grow up
要么你现实点
And make real money
赚实实在在的钱
And look after us
照顾我们
Like we've been looking after you for the past five years.
就像我们在过去的五年中照顾你那样
You know what these jobs are like, gaby.
你清楚这些工作的  Gaby
I'd never be home.
我会常不在家
And when I was, I'd be tired or irritated.
而当我在家的时候不是很累  就是很暴躁
It will take a toll on all of us.
-这会影响到我们
It took a toll on us
我们付不起燃气费的时候
When we couldn't pay the gas bill, carlos.
才影响到我们  Carlos
It took a toll on us
支票被退回
When juanita was sent home from day care
Juanita被人从日托所送回来时
Because the check bounced.
才影响到我们
But I handled it, and now it's your turn to handle it.
但是我解决了这一切  现在轮到你了
Gaby, please don't make me do this.
Gaby  拜托别逼我
Bradley? Hey, it's carlos.
Bradley吗  你好  我是Carlos
Well, I've, uh, done some thinking,
我...我想过了
And I actually...
事实上  我...
I want that job,
想要那工作
If it's still on the table.
如果还没人做的话
I was surprised, too.
我也很吃惊
Sounds great.
听起来不错
See you monday.
周一见
Hey, susan. I just made tea. Come on in.
Susan  我刚沏了茶  快进来
Lee, um...
Lee...
Well, there's just no graceful way to ask this, so...
实在没有礼貌的问法了  所以...
I'm just gonna say it straight out.
我直说了吧
When you spent the night,
那天晚上
Did we get it on?
我们那个了吗
Ye gods, no. Are you insane?
天哪  没有  你疯了吗
Oh! So... Nothing happened between us?
那么...我们之间什么都没发生?
Hello? Gay!
拜托  我可是同志
Listening to opera in a kimono.
穿着和服听歌剧的同志
What more do you need to know?
想什么呢你?
Oh, thank god.
谢天谢地
You know, when I woke up next to you yesterday,
昨天当我在你旁边醒来的时候
I just didn't know what to think.
-我真不知道该想什么
But why would you think that?
那你为什么偏偏那样想?
'cause you were mad at bob, and I told you
因为当时你在生Bob的气
About how I sometimes sabotage my relationships.
我也告诉过你有时候我会上错床
Ah. Well, you didn't.
你没有
Not this time, anyway.
至少这次没有
Now I can move in with jackson with a clear conscience.
现在我可以问心无愧地跟Jackson同居了
Good. Good.
好  太好了
Wait, so I just-- I have to ask.
等等  我得问问
Why exactly are you moving in with jackson?
你为什么要和Jackson同居?
Because...
因为...
He loves me.
他爱我
Do you love him?
你爱他吗
I'm getting there.
就快爱上了
Don't you think maybe you should...
你难道不认为在你爱上他之前...
Wait until you've arrived?
你应该先等等吗
Mike and I will never get back together.
Mike和我不可能复合了
I know that now.
我现在很清楚这点
And I really need to move on with my life.
我确实需要向前看了
You know moving on doesn't have to mean moving in.
向前看并不意味着同居
Jackson has made it pretty clear
Jackson说得很清楚
That he doesn't do good with long-distance relationships.
他不擅长谈远距离恋爱
I could lose him.
-我也许会失去他
So lose him.
失去就失去呗
I'm not good alone. I need a man in my life.
我受不了一个人  我生活中需要一个男人
But why? We're so useless.
为什么呢  我们太没用了
But you are fun to dance with.
跟你跳舞真好玩
I think you should tell jackson you're not ready.
我觉得你应该告诉Jackson你没准备好
And if he ends up leaving,
如果他决定离开
Then, hell, I will dance with you.
管他呢  我陪你跳舞
At least until someone better comes along.
最起码陪你跳到有更好的人出现为止
How does that sound?
你觉得如何?
If this is your attempt at bedding me again, miss mayer,
如果你又想骗我上床  Mayer小姐
I'm gonna have to ask you to leave.
我恐怕要赶你走了
Come on, man.
拜托  哥们儿
Mom really wants to talk to you, just for five seconds.
妈妈真的想跟你谈谈  就五秒钟
Do it for me, okay?
就当是为我  好吗
Sweetie, where are you?
宝贝儿  你在哪儿?
I don't want to tell you.
-我不想告诉你
Porter...
You have got to come home.
你得回家来
Everything will be fine. I promise.
一切都会没事的  我保证
How? Either warren schilling kills me, or I end up in jail.
你怎么保证?  要么Warren Schilling杀了我  要么我坐牢
We can get a restraining order to protect you,
我们可以申请限制令保护你
And bob thinks there's a good shot
Bob觉得还是很有机会
At getting the case dismissed.
可以撤销控诉的
You know, I've been reading the fairview papers online.
我一直在网上看美景镇的新闻
Everybody thinks I did it.
-人人都觉得是我干的
There is not a shred of evidence against you.
没有证据是针对你的
When people see that, they will be on your side
人们明白这个之后就会站在你这边了
Just like we are.
就像我们一样
Sweetie, you have to trust me.
宝贝儿  你得相信我
I do trust you. It's just i--
我相信你  不过...
Don't fall for it, kiddo.
别上当  孩子
I trusted her once, and look where it got me.
我相信了她一次  看看我的下场
Good morning.
早上好
Is it? I didn't get a lot of sleep.
是吗  我没睡好
Okay, about last night, uh...
昨天晚上的事
I'm sorry.
真对不起
Let me stop you right there.
让我打断你一下
I don't need an apology. I need an explanation.
我不需要道歉  我需要一个解释
And... If you can't give me one...
如果你给不出解释的话...
I'm thinking we're finished.
我们之间就完了
Look, I'm just stressed out.
我就是压力太大了
Stress doesn't make you talk to people who aren't there.
压力不会让你与根本不存在的人说话
What is going on?
怎么回事?
Okay.
好吧
Before we met, I was married to someone else.
在我们相遇之前  我跟别人结过婚
But she died.
她死了
And last night she was...
昨天晚上她...
Sort of on my mind.
出现在我脑子里面
You were married before?
你以前结过婚?
She's dead, edie. What does it matter?
她死了  Edie  这重要吗
Oh, it matters.
当然重要
You have until tonight
今晚之前
To get your things together.
你收拾好东西
Then I want you out of my house.
离开我的房子
Everyone needs a lovely home in suburbia,
人人都需要在郊区有一个可爱的家
Mostly so the neighbors will never suspect
主要是因为邻居们从不会疑心
What's going on inside.
屋子里面发生了什么
Behind these freshly painted walls
在这些粉刷一新的墙面之后
You will find...
你会发现...
Parents wracked with guilt...
深受内疚折磨的父母...
Wives tired of struggling...
厌倦了奔波的妻子...
Lovers who have been lied to...
被欺骗了的爱人...
Yes, everybody needs a lovely home in suburbia...
是的  人人都需要在郊区有一个可爱的家
If for no other reason than to have a place...
无非是为了能有一个可以...
To come home to.
回归的港湾